# KHOIRONI ARIEF

Lamongan, Jawa Timur 6283870461640 Khoironyarief08@gmail.com

#### ABOUT ME

Informatics engineering student at Universitas PGRI Ronggolawe Tuban, interested in programming especially web programming, experienced as a freelance junior web developer, succeeded in creating websites according to client needs. trying to continue to learn and explore programming languages in order to become a professional web developer.

## **EDUCATION**

S.kom

August 2018 – September 2022

Universitas PGRI Ronggolawe Tuban

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## • Dinas Pendidikan Kabupaten Tuban

February 2021 – March 2021

Magang/ PKL

Membuat sistem informasi administrasi untuk pencatatan surat keluar dan masuk

• Freelance June 2021 – Now

Web Developer

Membuat web company profile PT Bumi Harta Internusa perusahaan eksportir kelapa Membuat web company profile PT Sinar Ahza Samudra perusahaan bongkar muat kapal

#### **SKILLS**

Front End : HTML | CSS | Javascript | Bootstrap

**Back End** : PHP | MySQL | Codeigniter

Others : GIT | MVC | OOP

Design : Figma | CorelDraw

### **ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE**

#### • Komunitas Seni Rupa Roggolawe

Divisi Publikasi (Desember 2019 – Desember 2020)

Mengelola sosial media organisasi, Melakukan dokumentasi kegiatan, dan membuat desain untuk suatu acara.

Sekretaris (Desember 2020 – Desember 2021)

Melakukan administrasi berupa surat menyurat, membuat proposal, lpj dan lain sebagainya.

# • Relawan TIK

Head Of Program and APTIKA (Oktober 2021 – Oktober 2023) Merancang program atau kegiatan bulanan

# PORTOFOLIO

Website : <a href="https://khoirony.github.io/">https://khoirony.github.io/</a>
Repositories : <a href="https://github.com/khoirony">https://github.com/khoirony</a>
Design : <a href="https://instagram.com/fiktif\_b/">https://instagram.com/fiktif\_b/</a>

# LANGUAGES

**Indonesia**: Native Language

English: Novice Listener, Speaker, and Write. Intermediate Reading

# **OTHER**

Hobby: Reading and Painting